commvault.com 2017-03-15

# Privacy Policy | Commvault

Effective Date: 8/28/14

Commvault Systems, Inc. (“Commvault” or “we” or “us”) offers you the website http://www.Commvault.com/privacy-policy (“website”) and its content, features, and functions. This Privacy Policy sets out how Commvault collects, protects, shares and uses your personal information that you provide to us or that we collect through your use of our website. Our policy is to process the personal information we collect about you in accordance with applicable privacy and data protection laws in force in the jurisdictions in which we operate. 

You must be 18 years old or the age of majority in your jurisdiction in order to use our website. If you are under 18 years old or the age of majority in your jurisdiction, then you may only use our website with your parent or legal guardian’s permission. You are not permitted to use our website if you are under 13 years old. 

Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it. By accessing or using our website, you agree that you (or your parent or legal guardian) have read, understand, and are bound by the terms and conditions set forth herein. IF YOU (OR YOUR PARENT OR LEGAL GUARDIAN) DO NOT AGREE WITH ANY PART OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS OUR WEBSITE. 

### Collection of Personal Information 

Generally, you can visit our website without giving us your personal information or registering for an account. There are times, however, when Commvault may gather information from you in order to offer you certain features or to communicate with you more effectively as set forth in the “Use of Personal Information” section. The personal information we may collect from you includes, without limitation, your name, email address, postal address, phone number, and payment card details (if we permit you to make purchases on our website). We will also collect other information that may appear on your CV or resume supplied to us when applying for a job. 

### Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Technologies

Commvault collects information about the web pages that you visit through the use of cookies and other similar technologies. A cookie is a piece of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer. Commvault may use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies to enable us to collect certain information when you visit the Commvault web pages, including, for example: internet protocol address, browser type, operating system, referring site, date and time of visit, URL of pages visited, and downloads from our site. We may link this information to personal information in order to provide a better service to you and tailor product and service offerings to you. Below is a table to explain Commvault’s cookie functions and why they are used.

Cookie Function

| 

Cookie Purposes  
  
---|---  
  
Analytics and research

| 

We use Google Analytics to collect information about how visitors use the website. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the website. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the website, where visitors have come to the website from and the pages they visited. For more information about Google’s privacy policy, please visit <http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/>.  
  
Authentication

| 

Required cookies allow you to navigate our websites and use various features, such as use of authenticated areas, and using Commvault services. If you identify yourself to one of our websites, we use cookies containing encrypted information to uniquely identify you. Each time you log-in, a cookie containing an encrypted, unique identifier that is tied to your account is used by the browser. These cookies allow us to uniquely identify you when you are logged into the services and to process your online transactions and requests.  
  
Performance

| 

These cookies collect information about how visitors use our websites, including which pages visitors frequent most and if they receive error messages from certain pages. These cookies do not collect information that individually identifies a visitor. All information collected is aggregated and anonymous. It is only used to improve how our websites function and perform.  
  
Functionality

| 

These cookies allow us to remember information you have entered or choices you make (such as your username, language, or your region) and provide enhanced, more personalized features. These cookies also enable you to optimize your use of our services after logging in. These cookies can also be used to remember changes you have made to text size, fonts and other parts of web pages that you can customize.

We use local shared objects, also known as flash cookies, to store your preferences or display content based upon what you view on our website to personalize your visit.  
  
Targeted Advertising and Third Party Cookies

| 

We use third parties to track and analyze usage and volume statistical information. We sometimes use cookies delivered by third parties to track the performance of Commvault’s advertisements. For example, these cookies remember which browsers have visited our website. The information provided to third parties does not include personal information, but this information may be re-associated with personal information after we receive it.

We also contract with third-party advertising networks that collect IP addresses and other information from Web beacons (see below) on our website, from emails, and on third-party website. Ad networks follow your online activities over time by collecting website navigational information through automated means, including through the use of cookies. They use this information to provide advertisements about products and services tailored to your interests. You may see these advertisements on other web sites. This process also helps us manage and track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

Third parties, with whom we partner with to provide certain features on our website or to display advertising based upon your web browsing activity, use flash cookies to collect and store information. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. To learn more about these and their opt-out instructions click-through the links below:

<http://www.eloqua.com/trust/privacy-policy/opt-status.html>

<http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/>

<https://www.quantcast.com/company/opt-out/>  
  
Most browsers allow you to remove and block cookies and web beacons. If you choose to set your browser or mobile settings to block cookies and web beacons, you may need to re-enter passwords and user IDs when required. Opting out of cookies may impact the functionality you receive when visiting our website and you may also not be able to access certain website features or take advantage of information tailored to your specific needs. Our use of cookies may change over time, but will generally fall into the above categories. Please visit this page regularly so that you are aware of any changes. If you would like to know more about cookies, including web beacons or local storage devices, the following website provides useful information: www.allaboutcookies.org. 

### Use of Personal Information

We use your personal information to develop and conduct our business. Some examples of how we use personal information include: registering you for an account or for a webinar; responding to your requests; communicating with you when you contact a sales consultant or authorized reseller; improving our products and services; personalizing communications with you; conducting market research; conducting customer surveys; engaging in more targeted, customer-specific advertising; processing, fulfilling, and following up on transactions for products, support, and training; tracking and improving the effectiveness of our website and web-based marketing; considering employment applications; and complying with legal requirements and enforcing our website terms of use or otherwise protecting Commvault’s legal rights. 

### Sharing of Personal Information

Commvault may share your personal information with our subsidiaries, service providers and suppliers acting on Commvault’s behalf. We may also share your personal information to third parties for purposes that you have specifically permitted or when you have posted such information to our blogs, message boards, or other social media environments. Commvault may also share or disclose your personal information in the following situations: if Commvault has a good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary to respond to a judicial action, government inquiry or is otherwise ordered by law or legal process; to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss to us, our employees, or the public generally; to prevent or report suspected illegal activity; to protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety; or enforce any of our terms and conditions; with other business entities should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity or in connection with a partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy, or another corporate change. 

### Security of Personal Information

Commvault uses reasonable technical, physical, and other safeguards to help protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, and disclosure of your personal information. While we take reasonable steps to protect your personal information as outlined in this Privacy Policy, we cannot ensure or warrant our ability to do so because unfortunately no internet transmission is 100% secure and any transmission of your personal information via our website is at your own risk. 

### Your Marketing Choices

From time to time we send you e-mail messages about our products, services, and general updates. If you no longer wish to receive these communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication or you may contact us at privacy@Commvault.com. 

### Accuracy and Access

Commvault wants to maintain the accuracy of your information. If you need to update your information or correct it, you may do so either by logging into your account or sending an email to privacy@Commvault.com. We will make reasonable efforts to incorporate the changes as soon as possible. Where allowed by law, you may request access to the personal information we hold about you by sending an e-mail to privacy@Commvault.com. We will process that request in line with any local laws and our policies and procedures in place for dealing with such requests. Please note that before we are able to provide you with any information or correct any inaccuracies we may contact you to ask you to verify your identity and to provide other additional details to help us to respond to your request. We will only use this information in order to process your request. 

### International Transfers of Data and our U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Certification

Generally, the personal information that we collect will be transferred to and stored in the United States. The United States may have different levels of protection to your personal information than apply in your country. Your personal information may also be processed by staff in the United States working for us or for one of our subsidiaries, service providers or suppliers acting on Commvault’s behalf. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the provision of support services. By providing data or information to Commvault, including personal data or information, You hereby consent to Commvault’s use, storage or processing of such data or information in the United States (or in any other country in which we operate) for purposes of providing products and/or services to You.

With regards to any personal information transferred to the United States, Commvault is committed to complying with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework and U.S.-Swiss **** Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding its handling of personal information from European Union member states and Switzerland. Commvault has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of Notice, Choice, Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity, Access, and Enforcement. You may view Commvault’s Safe Harbor Certification at http://safeharbor.export.gov/list.aspx. For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s website at www.export.gov/safeharbor. 

### Children’s Privacy

Commvault does not intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13 and this website is not directed to children under 13 years of age. If we discover that a child has provided us with personal information online, we will take reasonable steps to delete this information. If you believe we may have accidentally received personal information from a child under the age of 13, please immediately contact us at privacy@Commvault.com. 

### Third Party Links

Our website may contain links to other sites, such as social networks. Please be aware that links to other sites are provided for information only and do not constitute endorsements of those other sites and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. The Privacy Policy presented here does not apply to such sites. You should contact these sites directly for information on their privacy policies and data collection/distribution procedures. 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will notify you by either contacting you via the email address that you have submitted or by posting those changes on our website. The Effective Date of this Privacy Policy is at the top of this page. 

### Questions

If you have any questions relating to this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at privacy@commvault.com or at: 

Commvault – Privacy   
1 Commvault Way   
Tinton Falls, NJ 07724   
United States
